#### Contact

jonne.paljakka@outlook.com

www.linkedin.com/in/jonne-p-b48632112 (LinkedIn)

## Top Skills

Linux

Web Development

User Experience (UX)

## Languages

Swedish (Elementary)

Finnish (Native or Bilingual)

English (Professional Working)

### Certifications

**HEMS Medical Passenger** 

# Jonne Paljakka

Head Nurse at AVARN Security Finland

Lahti Area, Finland

# Summary

I'm healthcare professional with 20+ years of self learned experience in field of IT. I'm currently looking for opportunities where i can combine my passion to technology and years of experience in healthcare. In future i'm looking forward to work as an developer

# Experience

**AVARN Security Finland** 

1 year 11 months

**Head Nurse** 

December 2018 - Present (1 year 3 months)

Jyväskylä

Head of healthcare services in Central Finland

Security Officer

April 2018 - December 2019 (1 year 9 months)

Jyväskylä

Päijät-Hämeen hyvinvointiyhtymä, PHHYKY

Paramedic

September 2018 - Present (1 year 6 months)

Currently on study leave

9Lives Oy

Paramedic

March 2017 - December 2018 (1 year 10 months)

Jyväskylä

Keski-Suomen sairaanhoitopiiri (KSSHP) Central Finland Health

Care District

Registered Nurse

November 2017 - January 2018 (3 months)

Keski-Suomen sairaanhoitopiiri (KSSHP) Central Finland Health Care District Registered Nurse June 2016 - March 2017 (10 months)

Lahden kaupunki / City of Lahti Registered Nurse April 2016 - June 2016 (3 months)

Mustijoen perusturva / Mäntsälän terveyskeskus Registered Nurse November 2015 - February 2016 (4 months) Mäntsälä, Emergency department

Lahti University of Applied Sciences Security Consultant December 2015 - January 2016 (2 months) Lahti

Yrittäjyys & Duuniexpo

Lapin Sairaanhoitopiirin Ky Paramedic June 2015 - August 2015 (3 months) Rovaniemi

Rovaniemen kaupunki Registered Nurse June 2015 - July 2015 (2 months) Rovaniemi

Kiviranta Kodit - Kriisi ja Arviointi yksikkö ESKO Registered Nurse Trainee May 2015 - May 2015 (1 month) Part of Bachelor's degree in nursing studies

Arctic Rescue Helicopter Aslak Registered Nurse / Paramedic Trainee March 2015 - April 2015 (2 months) Sodankylä

Part of Bachelor's degree in nursing studies

Päijät-Hämeen sosiaali- ja terveysyhtymä, PHSOTEY 1 year 1 month

Nurse anesthetist Trainee January 2015 - February 2015 (2 months) Lahti, Department of Surgery & Anesthesia

Part of Bachelor's degree in nursing studies

Licensed Practical Nurse April 2014 - January 2015 (10 months) Lahti, Acute 24

Registered Nurse Trainee October 2014 - November 2014 (2 months) Lahti, Acute 24

Part of Bachelor's degree in nursing studies

Registered Nurse Trainee February 2014 - April 2014 (3 months) Lahti, Acute Psychiatric Ward

Part of Bachelor's degree in nursing studies

Sydän-Hämeen Ensihoito Oy Paramedic May 2013 - October 2014 (1 year 6 months) Karstula

Keski-Suomen seututerveyskeskus Licensed Practical Nurse January 2013 - January 2013 (1 month) Laukaa

Keski-Suomen sairaanhoitopiiri (KSSHP) Central Finland Health Care District Practical Nurse April 2011 - January 2013 (1 year 10 months) Keuruu, psychiatric ward 35

Keski-Suomen sairaanhoitopiiri (KSSHP) Central Finland Health Care District Trainee in emergency & infection ward January 2010 - February 2010 (2 months) Jyväskylä Keski-Suomen sairaanhoitopiiri (KSSHP) Central Finland Health Care District

Trainee in department of Surgery & Anesthesia August 2009 - October 2009 (3 months) Jyväskylä

# Education

Helsinki Business College Oy

Vocational, Information Technology (2020)

Metropolia University of Applied Sciences

Open University of Applied Sciences, Information Technology · (2019 - 2020)

Lahti University of Applied Sciences

Bachelor's degree in Nursing, Registered Nurse · (2013 - 2016)

Jämsä Vocational College

Vocational degree in Nursing, Practical Nursing, Emergency Medical Services · (2010 - 2013)

Laurea University of Applied Sciences

Open University of Applied Sciences, Information Technology (2020 - 2020)